准备好点餐了吗
Hi, ready to order?
你们有什么特色[菜]说来听听
Do you have anything that's really special?
我高中辅导员说我没有特色
Not according to my high school guidance counselor.
那我要个蔬菜拼盘
I'll have the veggie plate.
不要甜菜 换甘蓝
But instead of beets, I want kale.
不要花椰菜 再放点甘蓝
And instead of broccoli, more kale.
蔬菜要用蒸的
I want the veggies steamed.
色拉调料改用柠檬代替
And instead of dressing, I want lemons.
你怎么还不动笔记下来啊
Don't you need to write this down?
现在只有心情写遗书
I'm afraid if I start writing that down,
因为要被烦死了
it'll turn into a suicide note.
我猜你们都会这么点餐吧
I'm assuming this table's gonna have a lot more of those requests.
没错 看你们那帽就知道是事儿精
Yes, I could tell by the hats.
厄尔 我有新东西想你尝尝
Earl, I have something new I want you to try.
正是因为这句话
That's the exact same sentence
我才会在几十年前 染上吸毒的恶习
that got me hooked on cocaine in the '80s.
我说的是 蛋糕的新口味啦
It's my new cupcake flavor.
女人无法抗拒的美味黑巧克力口味
Delicious dark chocolate the ladies can't help but love.
我把它称为"黑伯爵厄尔"
I'm calling it "The Earl."
说得好
I know you got that right.
我来了
Hi, I'm here.
本来我以为要迟到了 想说打个的吧
I was running late so I decided to hail a cab.
然后才想起我没带钱
And then I remembered I didn't have any money on me.
接着意识到我现在是两袖清风的穷光蛋
And then I remembered I didn't have any money at all.
所以我不辞辛苦地走来上班
So I walked the whole way here.
我家到这里才隔三条街
The apartment's three blocks away.
我知道
Yes, I know.
三条街 外加十五声"哟呵 妹子"那么远
Three blocks and 15 "hola chicas" away.
你不能再迟到了
Well, you can't be late again.
我够烦我每个月迟到的...
I'm already worried about me being late...
大姨妈了
every month.
在我来的路上 一位无家可归的流浪汉向我讨钱
On my way here, a homeless man asked me for money.
我跟他说 通常我都会慷慨解囊
And I told him that I usually always give,
但我的父亲因为非法敛财而被起诉了
but that my father was indicted in a Ponzi scandal
我们家产没了 曼哈顿豪宅也没了
and I've lost my family fortune and my Manhattan townhouse,
还得在布鲁克林区朋友家的沙发过夜
so I've been sleeping on a couch in Brooklyn, but,
尽管世事无常 但我还是对于
in spite of it all, I'm still optimistic
开小蛋糕店持乐观态度
that you and I will achieve success
并坚信未来将会取得成功
in our exciting new cupcake business venture.
瞧 看他给了我啥
And look what he gave me!
你连流浪汉的钱都拐啊
You took money from a homeless man?
应该说 是桥边的鲍勃入股投资才对
I prefer to think of Bob near the bridge as our first investor.
上菜 特制三明治
Pickup! Special sandwich.
我还想到一种更妙的三明治
I can think of even more special sandwich.
你 我 金发长颈鹿夹一起
You, me and the hot blonde giraffe.
她破产后尊严全没了
Well, she recently lost her dignity,
搞不好她会愿意屈就
so you might have a shot.
今天好啊
Hello today!
我给你做了个名牌
I have nametag for you.
你才来第二天 我就给你备好名牌了
Only your second day and look, nametag already.
这新东家当的 太牛逼了
As new owner, I am killing it.
谢谢
Thank you.
上面写的是"卡洛淋"
Oh, it says "Carolin."
我叫卡洛"琳" 是"王"字旁
It's Caroline. With an "E".
我叫卡洛琳
I'm Caroline.
这新东家当的 太二逼了
As new owner, I am sucking it.
你就挂着就是了
Just put it on.
不能告诉亚洲人他犯了错误
You can't tell an Asian he made a mistake.
不然等会他就去拔剑自刎了
He'll go in the back and throw himself on a sword.
谢谢你 李老板
Thank you, Mr. Lee.
你可以叫我憨
You may call me Han.
勇"敢"的"心"
H-a-n.
好记不会错
No trap in my name.
我在想 我们可以迈出
I'm thinking we should take
我们蛋糕事业的第一步了
the first step in our new cupcake business
就在优惠餐板上
by writing "Max's Homemade Cupcakes"
写上"麦克斯自制蛋糕"吧
up on the specials board.
不行 姐的大名不能张扬
No, I can't have my name up there.
我的债主们都以为我住在西雅图呢
Everyone I owe money to thinks I live in Seattle.
哎 以前西雅图是我家的呢
Oh, we used to own Seattle.
麦克斯 你的名字一定得亮相
Max, we've got to get the name out there.
制造名气嘛
Create a buzz.
好棒 好棒
Ooh, good idea!
赶紧开始名气大作战
Let's create a buzz.
没错 要想打开市场
Exactly, in order to launch--
我是在模仿你那傻样儿
I'm mocking you.
以后别怀疑 我向来都是在嘲笑你
When in doubt, I'm always mocking you.
说真的 麦克斯
Seriously, Max.
这个蛋糕事业是我们的救生索
This new cupcake business is our lifeline.
能助我们走上脱贫致富的道路呀
A way out for both of us.
我还想再次感谢你 让我搬进你家住
And I wanna thank you again for letting me move in.
如果有任何事我能帮得上忙的
If there's anything I can do to help you--
是指除了招待客人以外的忙吗
You mean besides starting to wait on tables?
我是说 任何能帮你平复
I meant, anything I can do to help you
和罗比分手的难过心情的事
through your breakup with Robbie.
谢了 我没事
Oh. Thanks, but I'm fine.
而且现在是我们工作时间
And we're working.
你不干活 我还干呢
Well, one of us is.
你确定你没事吗
Are you sure you're fine?
昨晚我听见你在哭
'Cause I heard you crying last night.
我才不哭
I don't cry.
早在两年前 我就把泪腺拿去器官银行卖钱了
I sold my tear ducts to an organ bank for cash two years ago.
当时我躺在沙发上
I was on the couch.
听到你在卧室里独自啜泣
And I heard you crying alone in your bedroom.
真的吗 那哭声听起来像啥样
Really? What did the crying sound like?
像这样...
Like...
我不是在哭
I wasn't crying.
那你是在干嘛...
Well, then what were you d--
哎哟 那事我管不着
Oh! So none of my business.
正确
That's right.
-麻烦记住这点 -收到
- And remember that.- Got it.
事实上 任何有关于
In fact, let's just say that anything having to do
我卧室 我桌子 或我生活的事
with my bedroom, my tables, or my life--
你最好都别多管闲事
you should stay away from.
界限 明白
Boundaries. Got it.
而且千万不要告诉任何同事
And please don't tell anyone at work
我让你搬进我家住
I let you move into my apartment.
一说出去 后果难以想象
That is one boundary we both don't want crossed.
为什么
Why?
嗨 同居"蜜"友
Hey, roomies.
懂了吧
That's why.
希望你能睡得惯这床单
Hope those sheets are okay.
不用担心
Oh, don't worry about it.
我知道你就只能买这么好的了
I know they're the best you could afford.
其实不是 更好的我自己用着呢
Not really. The good ones are on my bed.
麦克斯 烤箱太热了
Max, that oven is so hot.
你能帮我开开后门吗
Could you do me a favor and open the back door?
我们才认识两天
We've known each other two days
你就想开我"后庭"啊
and you're already asking for back door?
上帝呀
Dear God!
我忘了你是骑师芭比
I forgot you're Equestrian Barbie.
买芭比还附赠马一只
You came with a horse.
不行
No.
出去 小马 不乖哦 大坏马
Out, horse, bad! Bad horse.
栗宝
Chestnut.
没必要嚷它 它可是冠军马
No need to yell, he's a champion.
米田共臭度也是冠军
Champion stink bomb.
整个院子臭味四溢
It's smelling pretty ripe out in that yard.
这不关栗宝的事 布鲁克林本来就这味儿
That's not Chestnut, that's Brooklyn.
好吧 我现在就看见"冠军马"
Okay, well, I'm watching "The Champion"
拉出几坨热气腾腾的"布鲁克林"呢
drop some steaming hot "Brooklyn" right now.
麦克斯 对于把名字写在板子上这件事
Max, I've been thinking about how you completely overreacted
我觉得你有点反应过大了
to your name up on the specials board.
你觉得那是对成功的恐惧吗
Do you think it's a fear of success?
我穷到恐惧不起成功
I am too poor to have a fear of success.
我在沃顿商学院学过
At Wharton Business School, we learned
但凡创业都会伴随着一定的恐惧
that every new venture can bring up a certain amount of fear.
我能去Yelp网上给沃顿点个差评之类的吗
Is there any way to do a yelp review of Wharton Business School?
或许因为没人相信过你和你的梦想
Maybe you're having a hard time imagining
所以你才无法想象
this cupcake business could ever even happen
这个蛋糕事业会有实现的一天
because nobody ever believed in you or your dreams.
我瞎猜的
I'm guessing.
我能帮你美梦成真 麦克斯
I can make this happen, Max.
为了我 为了你 为了我们
For me, for you, for us.
你就接着烘焙超好吃的小蛋糕
Just keep making those amazing cupcakes.
其他我来做 做到你相信为止
And I'll do the rest till you believe.
我"相信"你说的每一句话
I believe everything you just said
我也"相信"孩子是未来的主人翁
and that children are the future.
麦克斯 是我
Max, it's me!
我知道是你
I know it's you.
你睡觉时 枕头底下还藏把刀啊
You sleep with a knife under your pillow?
这是我唯一付得起的家庭安保项目
It's the only home security system I can afford.
而且 割腕儿童欢乐多嘛
And I'm a cutter.
那沙发我睡不了
I can't sleep on that couch.
我想 "宜家"是脊椎"移架"的意思吧
I think Ikea might be the Scandinavian word for sciatica.
而且大街上有奇怪的声音
And there's weird sounds in the street.
我也没带助眠白噪音机
And I don't have my white noise machine.
只是波多黎各街头艺人在瞎吹奏嘛
Well, that's Puerto Rican noise.
你听听就会习惯
You'll get used to it.
我能躺在这睡一会儿吗
Can I just lay down here and get a little sleep?
我的男人都不准在这睡
I don't even let the men I sleep with sleep with me.
你的心里毛病我现在没力医
I can't get into your issues right now.
我只是想睡觉
I just need to sleep!
好吧 钻进来吧
Fine, get in then.
这是什么
What is that?
薯片 我边睡边吃
Potato chips. I sleep-eat.
清凉牧场培根味
Cool ranch and bacon?
拜托 好吃到做梦也会笑
Dude, they're delicious.
跟人分手就得自暴自弃吗
Because of your breakup with Robbie?
少废话快上来
Just get in.
我五个小时后得去市里给人看孩子呢
I have to be in the city to babysit in five hours.
天啊 你就像盏灯
Oh, great, you're like a nightlight.
金发亮得真晃眼
You're so blonde.
多谢夸奖
Thank you.
麦克斯 有人进了客厅
Max, someone's in the living room.
麦克斯 有人进了卧室
Max, someone's in the bedroom!
罗比
Robbie!
怎么了 宝贝
What's up, babe?
罗比 你来这儿干嘛
Robbie, what are you doing here?
我们已经分手了
We broke up.
还分着啊
Still?
没错 还分着 你调戏我
Yes, still. You hit on me.
然后她还发现你和别人
And then she caught you with someone else
在这张床上滚床单
in these very sheets.
希望你洗过这床单了
Which I'm hoping she washed.
我懂了
Oh, I get it.
你跟我分手是因为你喜欢女人
You blew me off 'cause you like the ladies.
没关系 我也喜欢女人
Which is cool. I like the ladies, too.
而现在 床上的两个女人我都喜欢
And right now, it's the two ladies I like.
罗比 如果我要玩百合情
Robbie, if I were gonna go lesbian,
她是我最不可能"合"的那位
she would be the last "les" I'd "bian."
听我说 宝贝
Listen, babe--
你伤她很深
You really hurt her.
闭嘴
Stop.
都是你 弄的她边睡边吃垃圾食品
She sleep-eats trans fats thanks to you.
给 把这些都塞进你嘴巴里
Here, stuff all of these in your mouth.
收到 你的事 我闭嘴就是了
Got it, your thing. I'll be quiet.
罗比 这样是不对的
Robbie, this isn't cool at all.
你都做出那种事了 怎么还有脸回来
Showing up here after what you did?
说得好 姐妹
You go, girl.
我说的话你最好给我听清楚
I have something to say to you and you had better listen.
你这算什么 恋情背后灵吗
What are you, the relationship ghost?
罗比 你走吧
Robbie, just go!
在恋情背后灵面前 事请不好谈
I can't say what I need to in front of the relationship ghost.
我会打电话叫你来拿东西
I'll call you to come get your stuff
到时候再谈吧
and we can talk then.
把钥匙留下
Leave the key.
坦白说 麦克斯 你伤了我的心
Straight up, Max, you're breaking my heart.
你是我唯一深爱的女人
You're the only woman that I feel this way about.
给
Here.
女士们 我不知道你们俩在搞啥
Ladies, I don't know what's going on here,
要是有我 一定更高潮迭起
but it would've been a lot sexier if I was in it.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
如果你想倾诉 我就在这儿
If you wanna talk, I'm here.
我能尝一口吗
Can I get a hit off that?
你觉得这就算好吃吗
You think these are good?
天啊 我们真穷
God, we're poor.
早安
Morning!
真是美好的一天
It's a beautiful day.
这些帘子的职责就是遮挡阳光
These shades belong down.
从现在开始 把我当作
From now on, think of me as a vampire
不用看我行销的吸血鬼
without all the annoying marketing.
坏消息
Bad news.
这街的水管坏了 所以今天断水
A pipe broke in the street so the water's off.
好消息是 我出去给咱俩买咖啡时
Good news, when I went out to get us two coffees,
两个市政工人 胡安和哈维尔告诉我
I spoke to Juan and Javier, two city workers.
最晚下午三点 就会恢复供水
And they assured me the water'll be on no later than 3:00.
我还去健康食品店
I also stopped at the health food store
给咱俩买了一杯鲜榨果汁来分着喝
and got us a fresh-squeezed juice to split.
是生姜苹果草莓味的哦
It's ginger-apple-strawberry.
这屋子上一位租客的
That was the name of the hooker
卖淫艺名就是这个
who had this apartment before me.
这是什么
What is this?
我给你的
From me.
上面写道 谢谢昨晚让我睡你的床
It says "Thanks for letting me sleep in your bed last night."
在我床头柜上留点钱 我会更喜欢
I prefer my usual cash on the bedside table.
我在那家可爱的咖啡店时
When I went to the cute coffee place,
我跟柜台的女孩 娜不浪鸡聊了会儿
I spoke to the counter girl, Nabulangi--
听以名叫娜不浪鸡的人开场的事情
If someone named Nabulangi is making an appearance
请容我坐好再听
in the first sentence, I have to sit down.
她说她的经理十一点会来店里
And she said her manager'll be in at 11:00.
所以我想我得换上香奈儿
So I thought I'd chanel it up,
然后美美地走到那儿
walk on over there,
介绍自己和你美味的小蛋糕
introduce myself and your fabulous cupcakes.
我"真"的有打算这么做呢
That's exactly what I was gonna do.
我去跟栗宝道个别就走
I'm just gonna go say good-bye to Chestnut and get going.
跟你说哦 只有一件见得人的衣服
You know, having only one cute outfit
省了好几个小时的挑衣时间呢
takes hours off getting dressed.
哇 外面好多新出炉的"布鲁克林"
Oh. That is a lot of fresh Brooklyn.
早安 栗宝
Morning, Chestnut.
今天真是美好的...
It's a beautiful--
不会吧
No. Way.
哇 屎奈儿
Look, Chanel Number Two.
告诉我 这是泥
Tell me it's mud.
快告诉我 这是泥
T-tell me it's mud.
不是屎吗
It's mud?
这是什么
What is that?
胡萝卜吗
A carrot?
泥里怎么会有胡萝卜
There's carrots in the mud?
没水
There's no water.
帮我弄掉 拜托
Oh, get it off me, please.
帮帮我
Please do something.
快帮我弄掉 帮我弄干净
Just get it off me, get it off me.
住手
Stop!
这衣服只能干洗
This is dry-clean only.
麦克斯 拜托 带我去洗个热水澡吧
Max, please, please take me somewhere they have a hot shower,
我求您了
I beg of you.
冷静 不过是泥而已
Calm down, it's just mud.
麦克斯 求你了
Max, please--
别碰我
Don't touch me!
你带我来你兼职的地方洗澡
Thank you so much for taking me to shower
我感激不尽
at your babysitting job.
我也是被逼无奈
Well, I didn't have much of a choice.
你都拿枕头刀来威胁我了
You pulled the pillow knife on me.
我会向主人介绍自己
I'll just introduce myself to your boss
并说明情况
and tell her what happened.
我不想让琵琪知道我带你过来
Look, I don't want Peach to know you were here.
这是工作 不是什么见面会
This is a job. Not a meet-and-greet.
明白
Got it.
我带你进去 给你五分钟时间洗澡
You get in there, you take a five-minute shower,
整理干净就马上走人
clean it up and go.
好 我先躲走廊 等她走了再进去
Fine, I'll hide in the hallway till she's gone.
没必要 跟着我进来就行
No need, just follow me in.
她从来不正眼看我
She never really looks at me.
早安
Morning!
早啊 麦克斯
Hi, Max.
快去
Go!
琵琪
Hey, Peach.
梳妆打扮
Uh, hair and makeup.
要出席什么场合吗
What's the big occasion?
去练普拉提
Pilates.
麦克斯 好消息
Max, good news.
人们发明了能让钻石更闪耀的方法吗
They found a way to make diamonds more sparkly?
我帮布莱德和安洁莉娜找到玩伴了
I got Brad and Angelina a playdate
是楼里的另一对双胞胎
with another set of twins in the building.
五分钟后见面
It starts in five minutes.
不错 他们叫什么
Cool, what are their names?
六楼B座
6B.
再见 布莱洁莉娜
Bye-bye, Brangelina.
妈咪爱你们
Mommy loves you.
伙计们 走之前
Guys? Before you leave,
顺便帮整整这个
stop at this one.
帮安洁莉娜整一下
Angelina could use a little help.
拿粉修修脖子吧 她太肥了
Contour that neck, she's a fatty.
琵琪 拜托 婴儿肥很正常吧
Peach, come on, that's baby fat.
可人家的孩子也是会以貌取人的呀
Still, kids can be cruel.
别听你妈咪瞎说 安洁莉娜
Don't you listen to your mommy, Angelina.
她自己老不吃东西
She never eats.
对啊 她自己不吃东西
Oh, no, she doesn't.
做好了
Here it is.
有"王"字旁的卡洛"琳"
Caroline with an "E."
我帮你重新做了一个正确的名牌
I have your new and correct nametag.
谢谢你 憨
Oh, thank you, Han.
哎呀 看到了不该看的东西
I've seen something I should not have.
我把正确的名牌放在柜台了
I will just put correct nametag here on counter.
对不起 但是谢谢你的"美好"
So sorry, but many thank yous.
你这是在干嘛
What are you doing?
我知道你不想被写上去
I know you said you don't want it up there.
但现在亲眼看见成品了
But now that you see it...
感觉如何
How does it feel?
感觉就是你不听话
It feels like you're not listening to me
去哪都不听我话
at this job or at my other job.
我说给你五分钟 洗完就快闪
I said a five-minute shower and get out.
你还在琵琪家睡了一觉
Did you take a nap at Peach's?
是高档柔软的寝具勾引我
The thread count was calling to me.
琵琪在她床上发现金发
Peach found blonde hairs in her bed
还以为她丈夫搞外遇呢
and thought her husband was cheating on her.
他是有乱搞没错 但这不重要
Which he is, but that's not the point.
你差点毁了人家貌合神离的婚姻
You almost ruined a perfectly happy fake marriage,
而且还可能导致无辜孩子受罪
and there are innocent children involved.
我有个好消息
Well, I have some good news.
瞧 那是娜不浪鸡
Look, it's Nabulangi.
我邀她来品尝你美味的小蛋糕
I invited her in to taste your amazing cupcakes.
只要她喜欢 我们就能进驻她的面包房了
And when she loves them, we'll have an in at her bakery.
-过去跟她打声招呼吧 -不行 我现在没空
- Come over and say hello.- No, I can't now.
我要在忙得抽不开身前 打电话给罗比
I wanna call Robbie before we get too busy.
告诉他什么时候过来拿东西
Tell him when to come over and get his stuff.
麦克斯 等等
Max, wait.
别 别打扰我
No, don't distract me.
我想让声音听起来冷酷又性感
I wanna sound cool and hot and all like,
"以后姐的身心你都得不到啦 蠢蛋"
"You can't have me anymore, sucka."
麦克斯
Max--
罗比 是我
Robbie, it's me.
录留言信息还打嗝 就你这么恶心
Classy burp on your outgoing message.
麦克斯 我
Max, I--
我想你明天过来拿东西
I need you to come get your stuff tomorrow.
少了单杠和香体喷雾的日子
I don't know how you've been surviving
想必是度日如年吧
without your chin-up bar and Axe body spray.
麦克斯 挂了吧
Max, hang up.
我打给他过了
I already called him.
你打给罗比了啊
You called Robbie?
你为我做了这么多
You've done so much for me.
我也想帮你做点事
I wanted to do something for you, too.
所以我打电话给罗比 让他过来
So I called Robbie and I had him come over,
把东西都还给他了
and I gave him his stuff.
这样省得再勾起你的伤心事
Now you won't have to go through with all that mess.
而且我还帮你教训了他一顿 开心吧
And I think you'd be pleased, I really let him have it.
你搞毛啊 说好的界限呢
What is with you and boundaries?
你不但挤上我的床 还睡了我老板的床
You're in my bed, you're in my boss' bed,
现在你又擅自打电话给罗比
and now you go and call Robbie?
你就像 你就像你那头大屁股的马一样
You're like-- you're like your big-ass horse.
在别人的地盘肆意妄为
Charging in everywhere you don't belong.
我以为是在帮你个忙嘛
I thought I was doing you a favor.
那晚从你卧室传出的声音
In spite of what you say about the sounds I heard
尽管你不愿意承认
coming from your bedroom the other night,
我还是知道你很难过
I know you're upset.
姐当时在自慰
I was masturbating.
我爱死我的工作了
I love my job.
我们出去谈 快
I need to see you outside. Now.
不要跟她扯上关系
Don't get involved with her.
她连流浪汉的钱都拿
She takes money from the homeless.
不是这样的 鲍勃是投资者
Not true, Bob's an investor.
马上回来
Be right back.
小蛋糕不错 对吧
Good cupcake, right?
麦克斯 有理智的人是绝对不会
Max, I don't know how smart that was,
把我们唯一的潜在商业伙伴吓走
blowing by our only potential business contact.
你把我的分手场景偷走了
You stole my breakup scene.
跟男人分手 仅有的乐趣就是
The only remotely good thing about breaking up with a guy
在还他东西的时候 告诉他
is telling him how much better you are than him
自己比他好个上千万倍
when you give him back his stuff.
我不知道你有没有注意到
I don't know if you noticed,
我的娱乐预算超级有限
but my entertainment budget is pretty low
所以我可是相当期待这一幕
and I was really looking forward to that.
结果半路杀出个卡洛琳
And then you went and stole it.
但我猜你是情不自禁
But I guess you couldn't help it,
你们钱宁家都是一路货色 偷东西的惯犯
'cause that's what you channings do, you steal things.
有意思
Interesting.
好吧 你这么想要分手场景
Okay, you wanted a breakup scene?
我现在还一个给你
You're in one.
我要跟你分手
I'm breaking up with you.
好啊
Oh, okay.
蛋糕事业终止 梦想已死
The cupcake business is over, the dream is dead.
我肯定娜不浪鸡会很震惊的
Oh, I'm sure Nabulangi will be devastated.
我不需要靠你 或你的蛋糕来生存
I don't need you or your cupcakes to survive.
我会找到别的出路的
I'll figure something else out.
因为 除了老被你瞧不起的沃顿学位
Because, aside from your constant Wharton putdowns,
我还是个商业天才
I'm a business genius
我一定会逢凶化吉的
and I will always land on my feet.
真的吗
Oh, really?
今早你还丰胸化屎呢
'Cause today you kind of landed on your front.
我们玩完了
We're done.
今晚工作结束后 我会打包走人的
After work tonight, I'll get my things and be gone.
你要拖着你满载梦想的小拖轮箱
Ooh, you gonna load up your dream-filled wheelie bag
骑着屎粑粑爵士离开了吗
and ride away on Sir muds-a-lot?
尽管嘲笑我吧 想多消极就多消极
Go ahead. Be as negative as you want.
你的未来你自己看着办吧
'Cause you're in charge of your own future again.
白痴 我穷得没未来
Oh, joke's on you. I don't have a future.
麦克斯
Max...
你醒着吗
Are you up?
不
No.
麦克斯 你生气啦
Max, are you mad?
是
Yes.
你醒着生气呢
Are you up and mad?
不 是
No and yes.
你的床好软啊
Oh, your bed's so soft.
那是我的胸
That's my boob.
我是搬走了 但我又回来了
I know I moved out, but I came back.
我把咱们死去梦想的余钱拿走了
I took the rest of our dead dream money
然后买了几杯鸡尾酒给自己和其他人
and bought some cocktails for myself and some people.
和自己
And myself.
那你有外带给我吗
Did you bring me back any of those?
不先喝醉我听不下你念叨
'Cause I can't listen to this sober.
麦克斯
Max...
我一无所有
I have nothing.
我真的很需要这个蛋糕事业
I really need the cupcake business.
我会改的
I can be different.
不 你不会
No, you can't.
嗯 我不会
No, I can't.
但我可以进步一点
But I can be better.
求你了
Please?
求你了 咱们放手去做吧
Please, let's do this.
我知道你对成功有恐惧
I know you have a fear of success.
你之所以这样 是因为没人相信你的梦想
You do, because no one ever believed in your dreams.
但我相信
But I believe in your dreams.
我们有个梦想
We have a dream.
天啊 你好醉
God, you are so drunk.
所以你估计不会记得这段话
So you probably won't even remember this.
抱歉我这么说你父亲
I'm sorry I said that stuff about your father.
你听见了吗
Did you hear me?
麦克斯 你醒着呢吗
Max, are you up?
你还有那个穷人吃的薯片吗
Hey, do you have any more of those poor people chips?
起床啦 宿醉第三集
What's up, Hangover three?
为什么把帘子拉起来
Why are these up?
我们不是吸血鬼吗
I thought we were vampires.
给 我拿昨晚卖小蛋糕的余钱
Here, I took the rest of last night's cupcake money,
给你买了一杯咖啡和一杯鲜榨果汁
and brought you a coffee and a fresh juice.
也就是说 做了两天生意
Which means that, after two days in business,
我们还亏了二十三块钱
we are $23 down from where we were.
所以我们还继续进行我们的小蛋糕事业吗
So we're still building our cupcake business?
当然
Sure.
我们一共只需要多钱来着
All we need is how much?
真是高"贵"的梦想啊
Which is awesome.
麦克斯 抱歉 我多管闲事了
Max, I'm sorry I crossed all those boundaries.
没关系
It's cool.
我已经和醉鬼卡洛琳协调好了
Me and drunk Caroline worked it all out.
事实上
In fact...
她还签了这份协议
She signed this paper.
我 醉鬼卡洛琳 是
"I, drunk Caroline, am a..."
这是什么词
What's that word?
臭显摆骚货
Punk ass ho.
谢谢
Thanks.
我 醉鬼卡洛琳 是个臭显摆骚货
"I, drunk Caroline, am a punk ass ho.
我保证以后不多嘴
I promise to keep my big mouth shut,
并帮麦克斯补回吃掉的穷人薯片
"and replace all of Max's poor people chips.
我以后再也不干预她的恋"青"
I will no longer meddle in her relation-chips."
在你狂吐之前 曾对此大笑不已
You laughed about that until you threw up.
我猜你心中可能有疑问
Oh, and if you're wondering,
请放心 呕吐污渍不会让这份合同失效
no, the puke stains will not void this contract.
天啊
God!
我又忘了我们还有匹马
I forgot again that we have a horse.
麦克斯 快把他弄出去
Max, get him out of here.
他还不知道我是个服务生
He doesn't know I'm a waitress.
栗宝
Chestnut.
他果然是匹冠军马
He is a champion.
学东西比你快多了 真有慧根
He learned that a lot faster than you did.